[{"answer": "Well, of course.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: (Inaudible) the order, Governor?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, I do -- I do and going by Obama's own standards, I think it's reprehensible.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Do you think it's reprehensible?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Yes, pretty much.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Do you agree with him?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Do you agree with him?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "There's a big difference.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "What is the difference?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "A category error.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "I'm having a what?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "A category error?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Explain to me why I've got my apples and oranges mixed up, that.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "I'm sure you've heard of that, right?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "For the American people?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "My point is that he wasn't the day-to-day tactical operative, guy running Al Qaeda.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "What's your point?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Yes, we are having this argument.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Are we really going to have -- ?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Because instead of making it -- taking a victory lap and getting the praise that he deserved for the decision, he turned it into this nanny-nanny-nanny thing against Mitt Romney, changing -- stepping on his own presidential message.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Why is it stupid?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, your characterization of what Mitt Romney said, I think, is off.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "He wouldn't have reminded his number one challenger that he said he wouldn't have spent the money?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "It didn't cost --", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "(Inaudible)?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "I'm curious what you're thinking what (inaudible).", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Are we really going to do this sort of high school debating tactic crap?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "That's cheap in comparison to what the cost of the war on terror is.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "That's cheap in the Republican world?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "No, but that's a timeline question.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Would you dispute that after eight years of Republican administration the country went into a huge economic collapse?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "I think the debate tactic of getting -- of sort of standing on a soap box and waxing poetic about how much I think this operation cost is cheap.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "I don't know what it cost, the mission, actually, but (inaudible) cheap is part of the problem here?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Maybe, yes.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "That's good journalism, isn't it?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, you're cross-examining me.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Isn't that the point of an interview about this kind of issue?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "I would think he would do stuff like that.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "I mean, are they really expecting us to believe that if Mitt Romney was president, he wouldn't do stuff like this occasionally?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I think as -- all in all, it's better to have a cool president than a not cool president.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "I mean, isn't this good for America?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "He's a stiff, to be sure.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Is Mitt Romney a dork?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Oh, the etymological differences are small.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "What's the difference?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I would think there probably is, yes.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Is there a difference between a stiff and a dork?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "I would say the latter is more of a geeky nerd sort of type.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Can you enunciate for me?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Could you be a stiff and a dork?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "No --", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Do you want to start chanting?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Yeah, man.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "But just to clarify you are a 100 percent bona fide Arsenal supporter?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, what I am is actually I'm a co-founder of a voter organization that's non-partisan.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Oh, I think he's a great speaker.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "What do you think of him as a speaker?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "I'm not surprised a politician would do that.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Are you surprised a politician would do that?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Would they work?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "-- huge.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Why aren't they voting?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Absolutely I think they have been.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "How are you encouraging them?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Well, we have National Train Day, which is the fifth one of its kind, coming up May 12th.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Why should I be talking about trains?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "It is definitely one of the greener ways of traveling.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Is the point basically that with gas prices soaring, gas guzzling cars on the increase, it's time for America to wake up, get real, get on the trains and start conserving that kind of wasted energy?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Of course I do.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Do you still get on the subway, seriously?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Well, in terms of being the best criminal defense lawyer, I leave that to others like Jeff if they want to comment.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "How do you answer those two charges?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I like that.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "You must have quite liked that poll, didn't you?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "I think a lot.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "How much of what you bring to the courtroom is down to that upbringing?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I think it's important for me that whoever the client is, even if they are powerful, important celebrity super star, that they understand that I am in charge until this case is resolved, that this is not business as usual.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "What process do you go through in your head?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "Every case is different.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Or is your job to ensure that the opposition, the prosecution can't prove 100 percent your client's guilty?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "It's a horrible case.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "What do you make of the Trayvon Martin case?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "I think it's a terrible law.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Do you think it should be scrapped after this?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "It's a sad case in many ways, because I think the perception of John Edwards before this case and before his fall from grace was that he is a pretty good guy and that he might have been actually a very good president.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "What do you make of the John Edwards case?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "It's much more difficult than it ever was.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "How difficult is it now to defend high profile people, particularly politicians, who are by nature polarizing, when you have this kind of overwhelming media onslaught?", "qSentId": 711}, {"answer": "God bless you, thank you.", "docId": "120430pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "What did he say to you at the end?", "qSentId": 757}]